<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	 <string-array name="PercentAcryArray">
	     <item>@string/PercentAcry_30</item>
	     <item>@string/PercentAcry_40</item>  
	 </string-array>
	     
	 <string-array name="before_protocol_array">
         <item>1) Clean all glass plates, spacers and work surfaces with ethanol. </item>
         <item>2) Assemble the plates and spacers into the stand provided by the manufacturer. </item>
		 <item>3)	In a clean flask, pipette desired quantity of ddH2O as determined by the gel calculator</item>
		 <item>4)	Add the Acrylamide, 1.5 M Tris pH 8.8 and 10% SDS</item>
		 <item>5)	When ready to use, add TEMED and APS- pour immediately (the gel will begin to polymerize after the addition of APS)</item>   
	     <item>6)	Pour the solution into the assembled glass plates to the desired height (typically to just below the level of the lane-comb, about 4/5 the way up the plates)</item>	         
		 <item>7)	Overlay the solution with 1-2 ml of n-butanol to ensure a smooth gel surface, aiding straight and uniform protein band separation.</item>        
	     <item>8)	The gel will take 30-45 mins to polymerize, any left over solution can be inspected to ensure full polymerization before proceeding</item>
	     <item>9)	Gels can be stored for up to two weeks at 4°C, but must be wrapped in wet paper towels to avoid drying</item>
	     <item>10)	Clean the lane- comb with ethanol</item>
	     <item>11)	Pour off n-butanol from the gel and dab dry the area above the gel with filter paper</item>
	     <item>12)	In a clean flask, pipette desired quantity of ddH2O as determined by the gel calculator</item>
	     <item>13)	Add the Acrylamide, 0.5 M Tris pH 6.8 and 10% SDS</item>
	     <item>14)	When ready to use, add TEMED and APS</item>
	     <item>15)	Pour stacking gel on top of separating gel and add in lane-comb</item>
	     <item>16)	The gel will take 20-30 mins to polymerize, any left over solution can be inspected to ensure full polymerization before proceeding</item>
    </string-array>
    
	<string-array name="About_array">
	     <item>1) Enter the number of gels that you want to generate </item>
         <item>2) Enter the percentage for the gel </item>
		 <item>3) This application has been build by www.jumpercake.com</item>
		 <item>4) The formulae for generating the gels have been provided by Dr Nicholas Tobin, biologist in the Cancer Centre Karolinska, Stockhom</item>
		
	</string-array>
	     
</resources>